♪ Please allow me to introduce myself ♪
♪ I'm a man of wealth and taste ♪
♪ I've been around for a long, long year ♪
♪ Stole many a man's soul and faith... ♪
Fire brigade, state your emergency.
Yes, there's a large fire in an alley
100 meters east of Bleekhofstraat.
Sending trucks now.
May I have your name, sir?
♪ Pleased to meet you ♪
♪ Hope you guess my name... ♪
Barry, are you there?
- Is the pig in the poke?
- Cat's in the cradle.
Geweldig!
- That's Dutch for "awesome."
- I know.
Took a competency test.
I'm at a sixth-grade level.
How's this gonna help us?
Job is finished today.
Turn right.
Increase speed 11 kilometers.
Alley is on your left.
Twenty seconds.
Double-time.
Fifteen seconds.
Ten seconds.
♪ I'm a man of the wealth... ♪
Five seconds.
Go!
♪ And I laid traps for troubadours ♪
♪ Who get killed
Before they reach Bombay ♪
Either you got on the truck,
or you the fastest
65-year-old white guy on the planet.
♪ Hope you guess my name ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ But what's puzzlin' you ♪
♪ Is the nature of my game ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Get down, baby ♪
Fire brigade has given us access
to Antwerp's Diamond District.
One of the most heavily protected
square miles in the world.
You'll be passing target
in three, two,
one.
♪ Pleased to meet you ♪
♪ Hope you guess my name ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
It smells like donkey ass down here.
So weird. I specifically requested
the good smelling sewer.
So, what time on Friday?
Six.
- Will there be ice cream cake?
- Affirmative.
With chocolate crunchies inside?
Of course there will be crunches inside.
What do you think, I'm an asshole?
I'm just asking 'cause, at Romi's recital,
the cake didn't have crunchies.
Stop.
Right above you.
Bun's in the oven?
King is in the castle.
Ready.
Powering up.
It's about to get messy, pal.
Sword of Omens, do my bidding.
- What?
- That's from ThunderCats.
Oh, for Christ's sake,
you're 38 years old--
Bee's in the bonnet?
Cream is in the coffee.
- ♪ You can only be true to one ♪
- ♪ True to one... ♪
Ah, guten Tag.
Guten Tag.
A gift.
♪ You can't be true to two ♪
♪ No, you can't be true to two ♪
♪ You can only be true to one ♪
♪ Nobody... ♪
Very nice.
My German is not great.
English is okay?
I'll manage.
♪ You gotta make a break
Make a break, make a break ♪
Mm-hm.
47.2988,
27.7499.
Oh! Our boy really was off the grid.
Initializing thermostat scan.
Peekaboo, I see through.
Target confirmed.
Air Force is locking in.
We'll be roasting marshmallows in five,
four,
tres, dos, uno.
one, human trafficker: zero.
My boss is where I said he'd be?
He's kind of all over the place.
To business.
Ah! Shithole.
Why is it beading on the diamonds?
Uh-oh.
Well, they are uncut diamonds.
- There is a film on them.
- Yeah, but--
Smells like tar.
This is a plastic residue...
from an explosion.
- No, you're mistaken.
- You don't own a diamond concern.
These are stolen.
Why did you lie about who you are?
Who are you really?!
Search him.
Something in the lining of his jacket.
What the hell is that?
It's cyanide. In case I get caught.
CIA?
Check outside.
Is there anyone outside?
All quiet. Nothing.
You came alone. What was the plan?
To get the coordinates,
kill all of you, and then leave.
Why would you tell them that?
And now, with all our guns out?
I guess I'll take the pill,
and get it over with.
This will be fun.
Cheers.
Nothing's happening.
Come to think of it,
I might have taken the antidote.
Shoot him!
♪ You can't be true to two ♪
♪ No, you can't be true to two ♪
♪ You can only be true ♪
- ♪ To one ♪
- Corn's on the cob.
- Candy's on the cane.
Now get on home. We gotta lock down
this ice cream cake thing.
- So, I guess I'm done.
That's it, and that's all.
You are correct, Officer Brunner.
Your orders are to destroy any
and all alternate forms of identification,
and return to the United States
as Luke Brunner immediately.
By the way,
the agency is throwing a party for you.
A few months of process and paperwork,
winding down identities,
and you are officially retired.
The CIA will miss working with you.
I'll miss you too, buddy.
- Pop, hey.
- Hi, sweetheart.
Where's my grandbaby?
- Backyard with Uncle Barry.
- Good.
Dad, hey. Good, wanted to talk to you
So, you read my proposal?
About the Maisles?
It's pronounced "MyAisles."
"My" and "aisles" pushed together.
Any supermarket, any city,
MyAisles app will tell you the aisle
the item you're looking for is in.
Don't the signs
that hang from the ceiling do that?
Come on. I don't want my family
living above the garage forever.
That makes two of us.
I have a PowerPoint.
I'll... I'll go get it from the apartment.
I don't want to invest in your startup.
That's it, and that's all.
Well, I'll get it anyway, just in case.
You scared me.
You're never gonna learn
how to knock, are you?
I'm sorry, I...
I was just, uh, trying to find a place
that I can put Emma's gift.
Up on the counter is fine.
Okay.
I'm so sorry I'm late,
but I had to borrow some wrapping paper
from my chatty neighbor from 3C.
It's no problem.
- Wow, that looks yummy.
- It is.
- Can I help you with anything?
- Sure.
- Just making some bruschetta. Here.
- Okay.
So how was your trip?
Oh, don't ask me.
No one wants to lift
heavy weights anymore.
Everyone wants to go biking
with their digital friends.
Can't wait to sell my half of the business
to Barry and to be done with it.
What?
I'm serious.
This time I'm really gonna hang up
the lifting belt.
- If you say so.
Now when is Emma getting here?
Soon. She had to go pick up Carter.
His car's in the shop again.
You know, a real man can fix his own car.
Luke, get it out of your system
before he gets here. I'm warning you.
I'll try, but for your sake, not his.
Attento! I don't like her up there,
Bartholomew. Please be careful.
Romi.
I want Pee-Pa.
Your wish is Battle Cat's command, Romance.
- Oh!
She doesn't like that.
She likes "Romi."
- Right.
-  Mm-hm.
-  I missed you.
-  I missed you too.
I brought you
a little gift from my trip, okay?
Okay.
- Ta-da.
- Wow.
You hide this in your jewelry box,
and when you're 18 years old,
I'll get you a really beautiful gift, okay?
- Love you.
-  Love you too.
That is a Congolese warlord's diamond.
It's supposed to go into evidence.
It was just one.
-  Sorry we're late.
-  Hey, there we are.
-  What's all this?
- Emma.
- Dad.
- Schatzel.
- Oh, I missed you.
I missed you too.
Now you're leaving.
I know,
but for even better reasons than before.
I lobbied the governing body
of La Guajira,
and I just learned
they accepted our program.
So fresh water
to five times as many Colombians.
Wow, that is fantastic.
- Congratulations.
They should call her the aqueduct.
'Cause she delivers the water.
- Are you ready to be blown away?
- Okay.
- Stay right here.
Okay? All right.
- I'm sorry.
- I thought it was funny.
- I laughed.
- Thank you.
Surprise.
Wow.
Oh, um... Ow!
-  You okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Your shoulder okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, it's fine.
I, um, I messed it up roller skating.
But I can still open presents.
It's a stand-up mixer
for the Sunday Funday bake-offs.
- Like the good old days, huh?
- Dad, I love it.
And I love you.
You always got straight A's,
first chair violin,
no smoking, no drinking, no cursing.
And now you're providing water
to millions more people.
It's one more reason
to be so proud of you.
But I have to tell ya,
I'm a little bit concerned
about this La Guajira.
- It's a very volatile area.
- How do you know about that?
My daughter says she's going to Colombia,
I Googled it.
Um, actually, the Global Fund has them
in a very secure location, Mr. Brunner,
um, and, statistically, most kidnappings
tend to be of American men.
That's great. Then you should go with her.
Luke...
I would absolutely love to,
but I gotta stay here and work.
Yeah, kindergarten teacher.
Those paintings don't finger themselves.
Dad.
Seriously? No crunchies?
It's not cake time yet, Barry.
One slice, Uncle Barry. Your heart.
It's the recital all over again.
This cake is bullshit.
Dad, I'll be fine.
And I hope you know,
I couldn't have done this without you.
Hm.
You've always encouraged me
and taught me to reach beyond my grasp,
and...
I didn't get here by myself.
I have a great idea. I'll go to the store
and get some cupcake mix,
and we break in the mixer.
- Chocolate fudge swirl?
- I'll be right back, okay?
- Okay.
I told him you wanted
a mortar and pestle to make Indian food.
- He doesn't listen.
- One of the many reasons I divorced him.
- Yeah, but he always tries his best.
- Yeah.
I love it, 'cause it's from him.
♪ What a fool believes... ♪
Mm.
I know, it's good.
So how are you gonna spend
your golden years, huh?
- Lots of mall walking?
- Learning the Facebook?
Getting vaccinated
for pneumococcal pneumonia?
Wilford Brimley Film Festival.
Are you gonna campaign
for Grover Cleveland?
You want to know what I've planned?
Here. Look at this.
The Oden 410.
You know, from the sting in Panama?
- Yeah.
Well, the CIA said I can have it.
They gave that to you?
I couldn't get a humidifier for my office.
Tally and I, we've talked about sailing
around the world together for ages.
Now since I'm retired,
what's gonna stop us?
- Fifteen-year-old divorce papers?
- She doesn't love you anymore?
The job's why we got divorced.
All the lies,
leaving in a moment's notice,
never having been around.
The CIA destroys relationships.
I've been waiting for a decade and a half
to win my wife back.
Tally and I, we're gonna make love
deckside before the summer is over.
Hm. I will never step foot on that boat.
It's not a boat. It's a ship.
- Luke, can I talk to you for a minute?
- Sure.
Hey, Aldon, Roo,
feel free to visit me at the marina.
You can scrape the barnacles
off my dinghy.
Ew.
- He's toast.
- Yeah.
That man survived a Russian mob hit,
but that Tally plan is gonna kill him.
And if it does,
I'm totally going after his ex.
Same.
If this is about the crunchies,
I swear to you, I ordered them.
We're gonna lose an operative.
- Who?
- Code name's Panda.
Been embedded in Guyana for a while now.
with Lape Pa Lanmo.
Remember this friendly face?
Omar Polonia?
I killed that son of a bitch 25 years ago
in Operation Jungle Book.
Not him, his son.
Boro?
Seems Papa's death motivated him.
Dedicated his life
to finishing what Daddy started.
That's impossible. I got him into
a boarding school in London.
- I know.
- He was going to study business.
He was going to be different than his dad.
You got half of what you wanted.
Graduated high school at 16,
Oxford at 20,
MBA from Wharton at 22,
all geared towards funding,
continuing and growing
what's left of his father's
paramilitary organization.
Lape Pa Lanmo now has over 400 members,
many living on his compound,
completely devoted to Boro,
the son of their fallen leader,
and to his cause of augmenting
their wealth, power, and influence
through illegal arms sales.
Specifically, with this suitcase nuke.
Complete with the reflector beryllium
to reduce fissile material mass,
thereby making it...
A WMD that can be taken anywhere,
and now Boro pulled it off.
Parental murder seems to be
quite the inspirational tool.
It's not my fault that the kid went south.
I even waited for him
to get off the compound
before I threw his father off the cliff.
Trying to be nice.
Boro has a man Troy.
He's in Yemen
meeting a potential bidder for the nuke.
Seems Boro's gonna hold an auction,
where the world's biggest and baddest
are gonna try to get their hands
on his weapon.
Intel says Troy's ascertained
Panda as a plant.
- Then pull the officer.
- We can't.
We've lost communication,
and since Boro forbids calls
from the Middle East for security reasons,
we have 36 hours till Troy's back
in Guyana and exposes Panda.
We need someone Boro already trusts
to get in his camp immediately.
We need Finn Hoss.
Oh, no way.
Boro doesn't know Finn killed his old man.
He'll welcome the rich European mercenary,
his childhood hero,
the man who looked out for him
with open arms.
I said no.
Whoa, wait.
You'll represent bidders who paid more
for the WMD than anyone else.
You zip in, extract Panda,
grab the WMD, zip on out.
You tell HQ I'm retired.
That's it, and that's all.
This is coming from WH HQ.
Patsy's Pastrami Palace.
How may I help you?
Yeah, I'm confirming a party platter.
Order number XK742.
Yes, sir, that order's confirmed.
It's very hot, and needs to be delivered
as soon as possible.
Damn it.
My ship.
Tally.
Hey pal, uh, I am 100% Team Luke.
Screw Team Donnie.
I promise your ship
will be waiting for you when you get back,
and Operation Life with Wife is a go.
What's Team Donnie?
What? Oh, I didn't say that.
I have a thousand ways to wreck your life,
and you wouldn't even know it was me.
That guy, Donatello, from Tally's office?
They're dating.
I saw them at Color Me Mine
a few months ago,
and I promised I wouldn't tell you.
Judas.
If you were distracted in the field,
you could've gotten hurt.
I was gonna tell you
as soon as your retirement was official,
but then HQ said
they needed to pull you back into Guyana.
Give me the damn file.
Roo and Aldon will be on standby
in case anything goes sideways.
And for what it's worth,
Donnie's snowman mug sucked.
Snowmen ain't purple.
♪ I'm gonna die alone ♪
♪ Really alone ♪
♪ I'm gonna die alone... ♪
That's Cain Khan, Boro's number two.
Be careful, he's tough.
Doesn't look that tough.
He clearly waxes his eyebrows.
Real men tweeze.
- No messing around.
- I'm not.
B Team's job is to observe and report.
I am observing
a physical characteristic of a target.
And I'm reporting he looks fabulous.
Like a Latino Zac Efron.
You can do Euclidean geometry,
but you can't figure out
it's not time to poke the bear.
- Do you consider yourself the bear?
- Maybe like a baby bear.
Swear to God, lock it up.
That's it, and that's all.
Finn Hoss,
I am Cain, Boro's first lieutenant.
- He awaits your arrival.
- Wonderful.
I didn't say you can go.
Boro knows you.
I do not.
Vámonos.
Oh, am I dreaming? I can't believe it.
- Boro.
I always wondered if I'd see you again.
Look at you, still a brick shithouse.
I still do the workouts you taught me.
Preachers, hammers,
curls for the girls, right?
Look at you, Der Bengal.
Der Bengal,
that's what he used to call me.
- The rascal.
- That's right.
Well, the rascal's done well for himself.
Well, thanks to you.
Everything fell apart after Papa died.
But you always watched over me.
You think I don't know
who was paying for my school?
All the care packages to England,
the peanut brittle?
Return addresses are dangerous
in my line of work, as you know.
I always knew you'd be there for me
if I needed you.
Come here.
You look so much like your father.
I really miss him.
I honor him by continuing his work
and hopefully doing business
with his dear friend, no?
Absolutely.
- When can I see the package?
- Yes.
I have a client who likes to avoid
all this auction nonsense
who'll blow you away with a big offer.
Of course.
But first, a tour of what I've built.
Quite an operation here.
I provide food, shelter, income,
and in return, my soldiers provide me
with unconditional loyalty.
We grow cinnamon, ginger, cacao,
the sale of which helps to launder
our extracurricular activities.
Me no habla.
Translate that Español, Mr. Linguistics.
It's not Spanish, it's Quechua.
What did he say?
He asked his pal if he wanted
to go shooting with him later.
Hell, I wanna go shooting with him.
Our own soldiers don't have that gear yet.
Just thinking about firing
one of those off gives me a gusher.
I also spy with my Goldeneye
tattoos indicating
Ecuadorian Special Forces.
Means even the farm hands are dangerous.
Download me later, okay?
Things are about to get real intense
real soon.
Grossed low eight figures last year.
The bombs in the Manila airport, us.
The AK's in Ethiopia,
on both sides, was us.
Impressed is not the word.
When I sell my weapon,
the most dangerous and most easily
concealed weapon on Earth,
the world will know
I'm a man to be reckoned with.
Russia, China, America,
they will all have to address me.
They will call me Boro Polonia. Polonia.
The name of my father
will be in the mouths
of the world's most powerful men.
Then it will be like he is still alive.
Come.
The boys are blowing off steam.
Dani, come on!
Make a move!
Good, Dani's fighting.
Wow. Packs a big punch for a little guy.
Just remember,
I love you, buddy.
Dani is not a guy.
Holy shit.
♪ I'm on my second drink ♪
♪ But I've had a few before ♪
♪ I'm trying hard to think ♪
♪ And I think
That I want you on the floor ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ Yeah, on the floor ♪
- ♪ Go on and take it off ♪
- ♪ Take it off ♪
♪ You gotta shake it off, baby, for me ♪
- ♪ Come on and break me off ♪
- ♪ Break me off ♪
How's my ass taste, bitch?
♪ ...what I see ♪
- ♪ Take it off ♪
♪ Take it off, baby, for me ♪
Do me a solid.
Dani...
someone I'd like you to meet.
Finn Hoss, Danielle DeRosa,
a real life American soldier
that decided if she was gonna fight
for a living, she might as well get rich.
Nice to meet you.
I liked your shoulder trick.
Yeah,
I've been working on it for six months.
Careful.
I know someone
that hurt their shoulder rollerskating.
Never got better.
Dani, she's the toughest one
on the compound.
And Finn here,
this is the baddest man
my father ever knew.
I'm always envious
about the way you talk about your dad.
Probably 'cause mine was a filthy liar.
General council meeting in the pavilion.
- Duty calls.
- Of course.
Dani, can you finish showing Finn around?
Tonight, we celebrate your arrival.
- Tomorrow, we talk shop, eh?
- Yeah.
Come with me.
You better be here to sell Boro a Bowflex.
- Me? Where's the irrigation system?
Oh, and this is Colombia?
Barry, answer the goddamn phone.
I know you're hearing us over the comms.
You knew Luke Brunner's daughter
was a spook, and you didn't tell him?
You know that YouTube video
where a gorilla
goes to town on a cantaloupe?
You're the cantaloupe.
Why didn't you tell him she was Panda?
I couldn't have Luke walking in there
with his kid on his mind.
Any loss of focus could've got him killed.
Pretty sure he's unfocused now.
My daughter's in the CIA?
Hey, buddy.
Uncle Barry?
Hi, pumpkin.
What the fuck?!
Hey, watch your language.
Lower your voice.
First, we are a quarter mile
from the compound.
Second,
fuckity, fuck, fuck, asshole, fuck!
- I think she's upset.
- Dollar in the swear jar.
Everyone, please, let me talk.
Luke, when Emma
got into George Washington,
she was living so close
to CIA headquarters.
It was too tempting for The Farm.
HQ watched the kid grow up.
Physical like you, smart like you,
so they set up a recruitment sting.
$200 for student testing
in the psych department,
and she took the bait.
Highest score CIA's ever seen.
Higher than yours, higher than mine,
except she doesn't have a heart condition.
You put my daughter in danger
because you couldn't handle the fact
that you couldn't do the job?
Her recall, problem-solving skills,
straight-up IQ, off the charts.
She was born to do this.
She's Luke Brunner's kid.
She took the job without hesitation
right after college.
Three years, CMO vault kept it
where you'd never cross paths.
Four years now in the field.
Global Relief Fund is her Merry Fitness.
You guys are CIA officers?
Yeah, for the last 40 years.
Uncle Barry for 17 years.
Uncle Barry? What--
- Explain that to us.
-  Yeah, you're really young.
Started working with Luke when I was 21,
she was 11.
It stuck. And Black don't crack.
Okay, how is this even doable?
The CIA created a Chinese wall
so you'd never know
I or your dad worked for the company.
Set it up where we'd never cross paths,
which was near impossible
considering you both work
for the same regional office.
Only a small number of people know
that both of you are on the job.
For the record, we did not know.
What is he doing here?
You've been compromised.
Troy's gonna burn you
as soon as he lands at 4:00 a.m.
Your dad is there to extract you
and to retrieve the WMD.
What?
I have been working this case,
sweating my ass off...
Language.
...and he's gonna-- Gonna extract me?
The hell are you so mad about?
I should be mad at you.
You've been lying to me
for the last decade.
And you smoke.
A decade?
- You've been lying to me my whole life.
That's it, and that's all.
She just "that's it, and that's all'd" me.
Who the hell was that out there?
"How does my ass taste?"
I mean, who the hell talks like that?
Luke, Emma often does what she wants
when she wants, how she wants,
and doesn't always listen when she should.
'Cause she clearly has daddy issues.
How could you pull my daughter
into this world?
The brass was infatuated with her,
and they threatened me with felony treason
if I leaked her identity to anyone,
including you.
My ulcers and intestinal issues?
This is why.
Your intestinal issues is because
you eat all the Sour Patch crap.
Hey, bottom line, the guy who's gonna
expose Emma lands at 4:00 a.m.
He needs to be dealt with.
But first, I have to go to the party
that Boro's throwing for me.
We'll talk later.
I thought you were my friend, Barry.
-  He's emotional.
He didn't mean that.
Yeah.
Listen, Boro is throwing the party
for everyone, not just Luke.
Yeah.
He totally meant that part
about not being friends though.
- That sucks.
- That does suck.
♪ We're gonna have a good time tonight ♪
♪ Let's celebrate ♪
♪ It's all right ♪
♪ Celebrate good times, come on ♪
Excuse me.
That was great, right? Come on.
It is a night to celebrate, no?
Because my father's dear friend,
a man who was like a second dad to me--
I mean, he taught me to drive on this
very compound when I was just a boy.
An ally to Lape Pa Lanmo
when we were first growing
and an ally today.
Everyone, Finn Hoss.
When my father needed resources
to grow our flock,
Finn was there to help.
Out of love...
out of loyalty.
And, while on the subject of loyalty,
I want to single out
one of our longest serving soldiers,
Jacomo Negrino.
Get up here, Jaco, come on.
Yeah.
Yes, there he is.
Jacomo has been part of our family
for over 15 years.
Moving product,
helping expand our territory,
watching every penny.
So the only question I have is...
where's the money?
I don't understand.
Where's my money, Jaco?
This is not good.
You manage it all.
Where's the money from the last sale?
It's gone.
I never touched it.
I would never steal from you.
Boro, no!
This is what happens...
when you betray our family.
Music.
Come on, music.
♪ Don't go changing ♪
♪ Trying to please me ♪
♪ You never-- ♪
Christ, Barry,
Boro makes Jim Jones like Jim Henson.
His profile did indicate
some irrationality.
He just opened up a man's head
after a Kool & the Gang song.
- His profile indicated that?
- No, that was a surprise.
So we're dealing with a high IQ
paranoid megalomaniac,
which is a bad combination
when we have two undercovers
we're trying to hide.
- You gotta put us in.
- There are risks to rushing in.
There are risks to playing
Little Miss Muffet too.
Just let me think.
I'm not gonna let anything happen
to the Brunners.
And how are you so certain?
Because family means no one
gets left behind or forgotten.
That's from Lilo & Stitch.
Kiss my ass.
Now, that's from Frozen.
Taking an interest in Miss DeRosa, I see.
Oh no. I'm an old man.
Oh, you're Finn Hoss.
My father said you invented a way
to slit a man's throat vertically
so he bleeds out faster.
You can do that, a girl's no challenge.
Your father also tell you
how much money I made for him?
I can do the same for you.
Just show me that suitcase
everyone in Europe is talking about.
Never get so busy making a living
you forget to make a life.
You taught me that.
Tomorrow, we work.
Tonight, go to Dani.
She's worth it.
I speak from experience.
♪ Don't change the color of your hair ♪
So sorry. Excuse me.
♪ Unspoken passion ♪
♪ Although I might not seem to care ♪
♪ I don't want clever conversation ♪
May I have a dance?
Sure.
♪ I just want someone ♪
♪ That I can talk to ♪
- I turned off the comms with Barry.
- Why?
Well, we may have to improvise,
and the CIA doesn't like that.
You know that British guy, the redhead?
William. What about him?
He slipped me a note.
He knows... that Finn Hoss
is a gun for hire.
He offered me money
to get his family and him out of here.
- He's terrified of this place.
- No.
- What do you mean, just "no"?
He's been here longer than almost anybody.
His kid was raised here.
It could be a trap.
He also could be a dad
that is scared for his family.
I'm sorry
if I don't have much faith
in the family concept right now.
No. You think it was easy to do
what I was doing with a family?
Trying to keep the marriage together?
You will find out for yourself...
the hard way.
We don't have time for this.
Troy lands in seven hours,
and then I'm dead.
We have to cover miles
through the woods tonight.
If we leave by 2:00 a.m.,
that gives us enough time
and lessens odds of us being seen.
Remember, I'm the senior officer here.
You got me word I'm compromised.
Your job is done.
I know the play for handling Troy.
I know where the WMD is stored,
so follow me or get out of my way.
♪ ...promise from my heart ♪
♪ I couldn't love you any better ♪
I think a farmer must've hit it.
You grab the horns,
and I'll grab the legs.
You could have just hid in the bushes.
I didn't know
who was gonna make the pickup.
Could have weighed
150 pounds more than me.
Element of surprise, this was the move.
Here, clean up and change.
We gotta load up the bodies
and move the cow.
Oh really? I thought we'd leave them here.
What?
Nothing.
During your little scuffle,
comms fell off and your camera broke.
I'm not comfortable
with you doing the rest of this blind.
It's not like I can run around
the compound with a cell phone in my hand.
I'll touch base with you later, okay?
Easy.
- I should have driven.
- Oh really?
Do we have to talk about
Mrs. Bernstein's cockapoo?
Maybe I wouldn't have hit Rosco
if you'd squeezed some driving lessons
for me in between all of Boro's.
I killed the kid's father,
so I felt guilty.
You killed Boro's dad?
Shit, how many kids have you screwed up?
Troy's back.
Go faster.
It's a bad idea to keep him waiting.
Well, talking about bad ideas,
what were you thinking sleeping with Boro?
What? I didn't sleep with that creep.
Good.
Now, you know I'm not too fond of Carter,
but if you're really getting serious,
you should enter marriage... before you...
What?
Nothing.
- Do you think I'm a virgin?
- Let me think what I want to think.
Oh my God, I'm 28.
All right, I'm old-fashioned.
When I got married, it felt special
that I was the only man
your mother's been with.
- Well, not anymore.
- What are you talking about?
Been divorced 15 years.
What'd you think would happen?
You're talking about
that schmuck Donatello?
Yep.
You're my daughter.
You're supposed to tell me those things.
Tell you what?
There was an Italian guy from accounting
giving Mom the old "sausich"?
That son of a bitch.
What does she see in that loser?
Maybe the fact that he's actually around.
Well, you know why I haven't been around.
Why do all the women in my life
have terrible taste in men?
Carter is sweet.
He's kind and gentle...
...and reliable.
And so is Donnie.
Gee, wonder why Mom and I
are attracted to guys like that now.
- Okay, now what?
- Suck it up.
Mom likes the guy.
No, I'm talking about the bodies.
You want to run the show?
Then run the damn show.
Fine. We throw 'em in the back
and ditch 'em in the rice paddies.
It's off-season.
No one goes there this time of year.
Double-time. Rain'll slow us.
Hey.
I'm sorry I cursed.
Dad, I don't give a shit.
Nuke's kept here in the north acreage,
away from the rest of the compound.
Best way there is through this stretch.
No one will see us.
- Set up?
- Steel construction Quonset hut.
Four guards, one at each compass point,
rotate every five hours.
All have AKs and MP7s.
But I've got one too,
and they can't shoot like I can.
They don't know I have this.
Where did you get that?
Black market in town.
I started skimming cash
as soon as they assigned me admin detail.
So Jacomo got killed
because you were stealing?
Apparently.
What? Jacomo was helping Boro
sell illegal weapons.
- What's that?
- The Charter Arms Pink Lady.
Small, easiest thing I could smuggle in
when I first got here.
Well, I think I should have the automatic.
I set the marksmanship score for my class.
So did I. And who knows even
if you're gonna be sober?
I mean, is this how I raised you?
Alcohol?
Cigarettes?
- And a garish lipstick--
- That's not lipstick.
- Oh my God.
-  It's vibrating. My God.
- Kill me now.
Purell!
Stop touching my things. Oh my God.
Tidy up before your dad comes to visit.
I didn't know
you were gonna be here, remember?
Transport is gonna be
at the airstrip in 30.
Can we please just focus on the job?
Yes, please.
Good because we gotta get--
- My God.
- Oh my God.
It's still buzzing.
- Oh God.
- Jesus. Okay.
Okay. Okay.
It's off. It's off, okay? It's off.
God, why are you here?
I never knew you hated me that much.
I don't hate you,
but I have every right to be furious
now that I know that
what I suspected all along was right.
You suspected I was an operative?
No, that it was 100% your fault
you and Mom got divorced.
But, Schatzel, now you know
why I was gone so much.
I tried to convince myself, you know,
"Dad has to travel for work."
"He's a small businessman."
"Clearly a very bad small businessman,
but, you know...
he's doing his best."
I wanted to beg you to sell that company,
to stay home.
But, you know, family situation
was tense enough with Mom always so sad.
She was sad?
- I thought she was angry.
- You could have taken a desk job.
Analytics, logistics, training.
You could've been home.
But no, you didn't want a desk job,
you wanted to run around the world
doing cool, sexy cases.
- That's not true.
- Yes, it is. You know how I know?
Because I like doing cool, sexy cases.
Difference is, I don't have a family.
I did everything I could
to make you wanna stay with us.
Sports, violin...
...math competitions.
But you loved all of those things,
and you were so good at it.
I wasn't good. I was perfect.
I thought if I could do everything right,
then no matter what
was going on with you and Mom...
How could you leave a perfect kid?
And now I'm an adult
still pretending to be perfect
because... I just got so goddamn used to it.
But you know what? That's-- It's great.
I'm so glad you know about my job
because now I can maybe
stop faking it in front of you.
- Sweetheart--
- No. We gotta get the suitcase ASAP.
Boro is gonna wake up,
he's gonna wonder where Troy is,
and it's not gonna take him
a long time to do the math.
Finn Hoss, get out here!
- What do you think that means?
- It means Boro's math homework's done.
Where were you last night?
Troy had an offer for our weapon
for millions, and now he's gone missing.
Who the hell is Troy?
I am a card player.
If we've never had a cheat in the game,
and money starts to go missing
when the new man sits at the table,
who do you think we suspect?
Usually,
the one who's doing all the talking.
Right now, you won't shut up.
I saw you exit the woods together.
I took your advice about Dani.
She is a tomcat.
That's why we were in the woods.
Maybe no one goes down
to the rice paddies this time of the year
because of all the flooding.
Sounds about right.
Move!
Move. Out of the way.
The cut on Marcos' neck,
is it vertical?
Finn!
Barry, we need an evac
at the airstrip now.
Go! Find them!
They do not leave this compound!
You find him, and you bring him to me. Go!
No. I slipped a note under his door
before we went after Troy.
- What if he's a loyalist to Boro?
- He would've shot us already.
They're not coming with us.
We're not with Boro.
They're getting close.
We've got to do this now.
I am so done doing things
just to please you.
I don't have my gun.
- I have to go hand-to-hand.
- No.
Barry, within 50 yards of our location,
there are probably
seven to eight cell phones.
The one with the weakest signal
will be wired to the nuke
and sheltered under a steel roof.
Fake an accelerated countdown sequence.
On it.
What are you doing?
Top of a hill,
there are two bulls that are looking down
at a bunch of beautiful cows.
The younger says to the older,
"Why don't we just run down
and make love to one of them?"
And the older one says,
"Why don't we just walk down
and make love to all of them?"
Know what it is about?
It's about not rushing into things.
Sounds like it's about cow rape.
Let's go.
- They're on us. Keep down.
- Emma.
- I'm okay. Just take him out.
We're bouncing all over the place.
I can't get a shot off.
They were able to hit me.
Shit.
That. Was. Her. Violin. Arm.
What?
Will understands.
Where the hell are they?
I'm gonna call Barry.
This is bush league.
For the record, I hated the mixer.